{
    "id": "Politica_81",
    "claim": "There are many kinds of democracy, the best political system after others, as Churchill said, but the one with the most appellation of origin of Spain is undoubtedly the democracy of the pucherazos. There's nothing strange about that, in a country of rogues, corrupt, cantamanas, meapilas, sellers of hairs and all that stuff. If St. Theresa of Jesus said that God is also among the pots, one could say that the communist revolution is also among the pots. In them there are pottages of very different composition, with various ingredients, textures and cocktails: we have what are the pucherazos themselves, but then we also have pronouncements, noises, frauds, revolutions more or less armed, coups de estado, motions of censorship..For a time, the pucherazo was an emanation of the Spanish provincial caciquiismo, typical of rural environments where the lords, the landlords and the rural nobility imposed their law. But when the workers' movement began to take centre stage, this perspective changed, because it is known that both anarchists, socialists, communists, separatists, and all that patulea have absolutely no scruples when it comes to taking power, and they don't care to organize a Potemkin than an assault on some palace; to organize an electoral tomato with street violence, which adulterates records and false accounts; or even put urns in the morgues, the tanatoriums and the cemeteries, so that the zombies also give them their confidence. This is how the military espedades, friends of marching for lodges that led assaults on power in the 19th centurySpartero, Riego, O'Donnell, Prim, etc. All Masonsthe workers' redeemers, the proletarian messiahs, who cried out against bourgeois democracy, saying that they cared about liberties, that they were democrats only if they won the elections, and wanted even a civil war as long as the Bolshevik red flag was waved in Spain. Nothing unusual under the red sun, as for murderers and torturers who raped nuns, dug up mummies, burned convents and churches, massacred in their Czech macabras, and executed for carrying a rosary and going to Mass without any remorse, organizing an electoral fraud was sinful minuta. The pucherazo is but a light coup d'etat, decaf, since this is a deluxe pucherazo, fine cinnamon of supreme quality, the apotheosic climax so desired by the palace raiders, performance that is undoubtedly more spectacular to be left in the history books. The left is also an expert in coup, because it is she who has starred in all, absolutely all, those that have taken place in contemporary Spain, since the National Uprising cannot be considered as such, because both the Republic and the Popular Front took power fraudulently, which deprives them of all legitimacy. It is elementary that the left should be pucheril and coup, because its supposed moral superiority comes precisely from the fact that it can do all the misdeeds it wants with total impunity, because, lacking ethical principles and the slightest scruple, having no respect for the laws that do not favor its interests, by splashing in the Luciferina sewers of atrocious atheism, they can execute their frauds as whistling, as if it were the most natural thing in the world, feeling entitled to the coup and the pout, because they represent the people, they are progressive, and all that rubbish. That is why the Left has never apologized for its barbassadas, for its innumerable crimes, and they give themselves the luxury of blaming their victims, as is the case with the iniquitous historical memory, for for for it the end justifies the means. In almost all the elections of the 20th century, all the victories of the left were due either to electoral fraud, or to a coup d'etat, explicit or not: The pact of San Sebastián of the year 1930, the coup d'etat of the elections of the year 31, when the monarchists handed power surprisingly to the Republicans when it was they who had won the elections, the coup d'etat of 1933 – when the left threatened an insurrection if it ruled the CEDA, which had obtained the majority in the elections –, the armed revolution of October of the year 34, the arousing fraud of the year 36..Since the Transition, all this democratic garbage of the pucherazos has continued, despite the fact that they are not sufficiently known, because modern electronic means allow to erase the traces of this misdemeanour, since it is no longer carried out the presentation of an electoral record showing brazen tachaduras, additions, scrapes and amendments, as happened in the fraudulent elections of the year 36. Thus, the 23F was an authentic self-coup of state with which it was intended to favor the coming to power of the socialists, as well as the 11M, which allowed access to the power of the Zapatistas, and the same can be said of the coup hidden in the motion of fateful censorship that brought us the nauseating Sanchismo. Hit by blow, and not verse by verse, is how the Reds want to take our homeland to the Tartaros landfills, that is, the NOM. And along with the beatings, there are suspicions of punching: in 1993 there were serious irregularities in the census of some provinces, where whole right-wing neighborhoods were erased from the electoral census. In these elections the Electoral Board accused the PSOE of violating information neutrality, reaching limits that blushed to their own and strangers, according to the TVE workers themselves. The most typical thing about punching is that it affects those seats that are decided for a very small amount of votes. In this sense, the most suspicious elections were those of 1996, where polls skated in a loud way, winning Jose María Aznar only for fifteen seats, when the polls gave him a far greater advantage. This last-minute vote change was very significant, as well as suspicious, as there was a spectacular turnaround at the last moment of the vote. The height of the hills is that these red messiahs also cheat among themselves, organizing pucherazos even in the same primaries that organize to elect their leaders. It is well known the scandal that Zapatero organized when he was elected as the PSOE leader in Leon, arriving to put ballot boxes in the cemeteries so that the dead could vote for him. But we hadn't seen anything yetexcept for the ultramegagolpist Largo Caballerobecause pucheril perfection is in Sanchez, a liar and dancer, perfectus detritus de la dictacracia, Rasputin quasi tavernario, a Faustic character like Luis candelas, felon, megalomaniac, narcissist..as much as adjectives I put it, I will never stop describing him as he deserves, but undoubtedly the one that best fits him is the one dedicated to him by many articulists: psychopath. From caste comes to the greyhound, as Sánchez starred in an alevoso pucherazo at the same headquarters of Ferraz in October 2016, when, behind a screen, and without any authorization, Sánchez's supporters began a vote in an urn on the holding of an extraordinary express Congress. Vote without control, without censors, without intervention, this pucheraz provoked disgust and tears even among the members closest to it. Then came his doctoral thesis, pucherazo cum laude, but it is not necessary to forget his activity in Caja Madrid at the same time of the scandal of the preferential ones, neither the plugs to the Begoñísima, nor that it was surrounded by a cabinet cum fraud without parallel, where many of its components are addicted to the fiscal pucheras of creating ghost societies to evade taxes. The PSOE raised this evil crow that seeks to take our eyes, our moneys, and the Spains. In his impressive career as a macarra rasputinesca, the icing was the coup d'etat he disguised with the motion of censure. Such a sinister character, with a total lack of scruples, is more than willing to falsify an election, to organize the punch that it takes for no one to get him out of his Falcon, would be missing more. Can anyone doubt it?Now, in a country like Spain, is it possible that a pucheraz can be produced?The reality is that, since Tezanos arrived at the CIS, every month we are attending a pucheraso of law, with those crazy polls that yield scandalously rigged results in favor of the PSOE, which they do not believe themselves. But, spinning thinner, one wonders whether these predictions are but a way to make a possible socialist punch more credible, advancing those incredible results so that later, when they materialize, they do not cause so much as amazement or indignation, using the tactics of the already said, and arguing that the hidden vote was of the PSOE. Naturally, in the elections of 28-A there will be acts of picaresca, not to mention otherwise, on the part of supporters of the left against ballots of center-right: theft, manipulations in order to turn them into invalid ballots, harassment at the exit of the governors of the schools after the writing of the minutes.. A whole host of macarrero acts in which the left is so expert. There may even be zombies who abandon their tannatories and fields to exercise their democratic right. Nor should it be ruled out that all immigrants who can, even if they do not have the right to vote, should be included in the census, since it is clear that this group is voting on the left. For putting up a case, we already had the Guadalajara scandal. But while it is highly unlikely that the votes of polling stations can be manipulated, since everything is done by hand, the same is not the case when the results of the electoral records are sent to the Matrix of the Ministry of the Interior, where the company in charge of counting the votes and awarding the seats will be located, since this process is carried out by a company, which is well aware of the cracks and fissures through which the votes can be changed, a process which, moreover, will be in the hands of a handful of people. Surprisingly, for the elections, the State has terminated the contract with Indra, the traditional company that has been in charge of this task for quite some time, and that, despite the fact that it has not been able to avoid suspicions in some electoral processes in which it intervenedin Hispanic America above allit was doing badly that its task was well. Now the dealership is the company SCYTL, also Catalan and linked to George Soros, which organized an electronic vote election in Switzerland that turned out to be a fiasco, for its lack of security. But the pearl of this possible hacking that awaits us is in the anti-hacking decree that has been pulled out of the sleeve of the government, in order to protect the electoral results from possible cyber attacks, claiming that they have already occurred in some elections in other countries. According to this decree, a new body - the Sub-Committee on Information Security in Electoral Processes, attached to the Higher Committee for Information Security - consisting of six senior officials appointed by the Government, will draw up a protocol against the falsification of electoral data, and will have the power to suspend the publication of provisional data on the ballot, which means that we may not know the results until a couple of days later, when the final data are given, passing a margin of two days in the interim during which the results can be cooked. Another suspicion lies in the obvious fact that it will not be possible to know with certainty the veracity of that alleged attack by the hackers, or its extent, if it actually occurs. Under what criteria will it be determined whether or not to suspend provisional scrutiny?What guarantees of reliability does a computer program have that clearly admits its weakness to a cyber attack on the Ministry of the Interior, or its website?The case is that we will have two days of darkness where Spain will be in the belly of the whale, from a monstrous Matrix, from which another Popular Front can emerge. Just as no one in his right mind would buy Sanchez a used car, it is impossible for a citizen aware minimally of his rufianesque calaña not to harbour suspicion that this psychopath is willing to everything in order to continue to feel the unceasing caress of the Monclovita velvet. The possibility that Sánchez is plotting something fat is a rumor that grows with the passing of the days, even from people close to the Moncloa, an unstoppable runrun that sets many patriots on the edge, a tidal wave that threatens to turn into reality the nightmare of attending a red-separate revolution in Spain, which would undoubtedly lead us to a pre-war situation. And it is that the PSOE, that of the hundred years of beating and barbarism, that of the thousand and a pucherazos, can be defined perfectly with this sentence of the movie Death among the flowers: It is a cheater, just like his brother. I'm sorry.",
    "source": "www.alertadigital.com",
    "date": "23/04/2019",
    "veracity": 0,
    "claims": [
        {
            "claim": "There are many the Left of democracy, the best political system after the Left , as Churchill zombies who abandon their tannatories and fields to exercise their democratic right an electronic vote election in Switzerland that turned out to be a fiasco, for its lack of security .",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "What did alertadigital say about the Left of democracy?",
                    "answer": "the best political system after the Left"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What was the purpose of the electronic vote election in Switzerland in 2019?",
                    "score": 0.6824,
                    "answers": "to exercise their democratic right an electronic vote election in Switzerland that turned out to be a fiasco , for its lack of security|advcl\tfor its lack of security|prep\tits lack of security|pobj\tof security|prep\tsecurity|pobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the best political system after the Left of democracy?",
                    "score": 0.6467,
                    "answers": "www.alertadigital.com reported on 23/04/2019 that There are many the Left of democracy , the best political system after the Left , as Churchill zombies who abandon their tannatories and fields to exercise their democratic right an electronic vote election in Switzerland that turned out to be a fiasco , for its lack of security|ROOT\t23/04/2019|pobj\tthat|mark\tThere|expl\tmany|amod\tthe|det\tmany the Left of democracy , the best political system after the Left ,|attr\t,|punct\tthe|det\tbest|amod\tpolitical|amod\tafter the Left|prep\tthe|det\tthe Left|pobj\t,|punct\tas Churchill zombies who abandon their tannatories and fields to exercise their democratic right an electronic vote election in Switzerland that turned out to be a fiasco , for its lack of security|prep\tChurchill zombies who abandon their tannatories and fields to exercise their democratic right an electronic vote election in Switzerland that turned out to be a fiasco , for its lack of security|pobj\twho|nsubj\twho abandon their tannatories and fields to exercise their democratic right an electronic vote election in Switzerland that turned out to be a fiasco , for its lack of security|relcl\ttheir|poss\tand|cc\tfields|conj\tto|aux\ttheir|poss\tdemocratic|amod\ttheir democratic right an electronic vote election in Switzerland that turned out to be a fiasco , for its lack of security|dobj\tan|det\telectronic|amod\tvote|compound\tin Switzerland|prep\tthat|nsubj\tthat turned out to be a fiasco , for its lack of security|relcl\tout|prt\tto|aux\tto be a fiasco|xcomp\ta|det\ta fiasco|attr\t,|punct\tits|poss"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is Alertadigital.com?",
                    "score": 0.4774,
                    "answers": "www.alertadigital.com|nsubj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "all immigrants who can, even if they do not have the right to vote Spain they Spain his Spain they Spain .",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "What did www.alertadigital.com report on 23/04/2019?",
                    "answer": "all immigrants who can, even if they do not have the right to vote Spain"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "How many immigrants can vote in Spain?",
                    "score": 0.8264,
                    "answers": "all immigrants who can|dep"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What are the voting rights of immigrants who can not vote in Spain?",
                    "score": 0.8215,
                    "answers": "on 23/04/2019|prep\tall|det"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What does Alertadigital.com say about immigrants voting in Spain?",
                    "score": 0.7981,
                    "answers": "www.alertadigital.com reported on 23/04/2019 that all immigrants who can , even if they do not have the right to vote Spain they Spain his Spain they Spain|ROOT\t,|punct"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is Spain's right to vote?",
                    "score": 0.7409,
                    "answers": "Spain they Spain his Spain|dobj\tthey Spain his Spain|appos"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the right to vote in Spain?",
                    "score": 0.7304,
                    "answers": "that|mark\twho|nsubj\twho can|relcl\teven|advmod\tif|mark\tthey|nsubj\tdo|aux\tnot|neg\tthe|det\tthe right to vote|dobj\tto|aux\tto vote|acl\tthey|nmod\this|poss\tthey|nsubj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "the government of Jesus said that God is also among the pots the PSOE possible cyber attacks communist revolution is also among the pots his .",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "What did the government of Jesus say God is also among the pots of?",
                    "answer": "cyber attacks communist revolution"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What does the government of Jesus say about cyberciphers?",
                    "score": 0.7354,
                    "answers": "that the government of Jesus said that God is also among the pots the PSOE possible cyber attacks communist revolution is also among the pots his|ccomp"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What does Alertadigital.com say about God being among the pots the PSOE possible cyber attacks?",
                    "score": 0.7211,
                    "answers": "his|appos"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What are the pots that God is among the pots his is?",
                    "score": 0.6454,
                    "answers": "the pots his|pobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the acronym \"PSOE\"?",
                    "score": 0.6338,
                    "answers": "the pots|pobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the name of the government of Jesus?",
                    "score": 0.6311,
                    "answers": "the government of Jesus|nsubj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "In the pots the PSOE the elections of the year 31 him the TVE workers themselves an alevoso pucherazo textures the Republicans punching have what the Republicans the pucherazos the elections of the year 31 the PSOE but then the PSOE also have pronouncementsthe PSOE him , revolutions more or less armed, coups de the government of censorship..For a time, the pucherazo Jose María Aznar of the those incredible results an alevoso pucherazo the year 36 environments those incredible results all this democratic garbage of the pucherazos imposed the results .",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "What does the PSOE also have?",
                    "answer": "pronouncementsthe PSOE him"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What does the PSOE also have?",
                    "answer": "pronouncementsthe PSOE him"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What does the PSOE also have?",
                    "answer": "pronouncementsthe PSOE him"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "How many votes did Jose María Aznar receive in the elections of the year 36?",
                    "score": 0.7214,
                    "answers": "a time|pobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What was the results of the Pucherazo in the year 36 environments?",
                    "score": 0.7077,
                    "answers": "those incredible results an alevoso pucherazo the year 36 environments those incredible results all this democratic garbage of the pucherazos|pobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What was the result of the Pucherazo Jose María Aznar?",
                    "score": 0.6994,
                    "answers": "For a time , the pucherazo Jose María Aznar of the those incredible results an alevoso pucherazo the year 36 environments those incredible results all this democratic garbage of the pucherazos imposed the results|ROOT"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What did the Republicans say about the Pucherazos?",
                    "score": 0.689,
                    "answers": "punching|dep"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the name of the government that controls the PSOE elections?",
                    "score": 0.6755,
                    "answers": "of censorship|prep"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "But when the workers' movement began to take centre him The left the PSOE changed, because it is known these red messiahs the results both anarchists, socialists, communists, separatists, and all that patulea these red messiahs both anarchists, socialists, communists, separatists, and all that patulea the Begoñísima both anarchists, socialists, communists, separatists, and all that patulea have absolutely no a cabinet cum fraud without parallel ballots of center-right a cabinet cum fraud without parallel , and both anarchists, socialists, communists, separatists, and all that patulea doa cabinet cum fraud without parallel that alleged attack by the hackers both the Republic and the Popular Front that alleged attack by the hackers both the Republic and the Popular Front some that alleged attack by the hackers it the PSOE organize the 23F electoral tomato with street violence, which adulterates records The left false accountsZapatero even put urns in The left morgues, the a computer program cemeteries, so that the zombies a computer program also give both anarchists, socialists, communists, separatists, and all that patulea confidence.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "What did the Begosima have absolutely no of?",
                    "answer": "a cabinet cum fraud without parallel ballots of center-right a cabinet cum fraud without parallel"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What did the Begosima have absolutely no of?",
                    "answer": "a cabinet cum fraud without parallel ballots of center-right a cabinet cum fraud without parallel"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What did hackers do to steal the 23F electoral tomatoes?",
                    "score": 0.6611,
                    "answers": "by the hackers both the Republic and the Popular Front|prep\tby the hackers both the Republic and the Popular Front|prep"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the name of the red messiahs who are both anarchists, socialists, communists, and separatists?",
                    "score": 0.6607,
                    "answers": "all that patulea|conj\tall that patulea|conj\tall that patulea|conj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What are the results of the red messiahs?",
                    "score": 0.6581,
                    "answers": "www.alertadigital.com|nsubj\tbecause it is known these red messiahs the results|advcl\tred|amod\tthese red messiahs the results|npadvmod\tthe results|appos\tsocialists , communists , separatists , and all that patulea|conj\tcommunists , separatists , and all that patulea|conj\tseparatists , and all that patulea|conj\tred|amod\tsocialists , communists , separatists , and all that patulea|conj\tcommunists , separatists , and all that patulea|conj\tseparatists , and all that patulea|conj\tof center - right|prep\ta cabinet|nmod\tcum fraud|appos\t23F|nmod\tcomputer program|compound\tsocialists , communists , separatists , and all that patulea|conj\tcommunists , separatists , and all that patulea|conj\tseparatists , and all that patulea|conj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What are the red messiahs?",
                    "score": 0.6568,
                    "answers": "him The left|dobj\tthese|det\tthese|det\tthese red messiahs both anarchists , socialists , communists , separatists , and all that patulea the Begoñísima both anarchists , socialists , communists , separatists , and all that patulea|appos\tsocialists , communists , separatists , and all that patulea the Begoñísima|conj\turns|dobj\ta computer program|nsubj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What did hackers say about the 23F electoral tomato?",
                    "score": 0.6532,
                    "answers": "both anarchists , socialists , communists , separatists , and all that patulea doa cabinet cum fraud without parallel that alleged attack by the hackers both the Republic and the Popular Front that alleged attack by the hackers both the Republic and the Popular Front some that alleged attack by the hackers it the PSOE organize the 23F electoral tomato with street violence , which adulterates records|conj\tthat alleged attack by the hackers both the Republic and the Popular Front that alleged attack by the hackers both the Republic and the Popular Front some that alleged attack by the hackers it the PSOE organize the 23F electoral tomato with street violence , which adulterates records|appos\tthat alleged attack by the hackers both the Republic and the Popular Front some that alleged attack by the hackers it the PSOE organize the 23F electoral tomato with street violence , which adulterates records|appos\tsome that alleged attack by the hackers it the PSOE organize the 23F electoral tomato with street violence , which adulterates records|appos\tthat alleged attack by the hackers it the PSOE organize the 23F electoral tomato with street violence , which adulterates records|appos"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "the Ministry of the Interior , friends of marching for lodges that led assaults on power in the 19th centurySpartero, Riego, O'Donnell, Prim, etc.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Who led assaults on power in the 19th century?",
                    "answer": "Ministry of the Interior"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "Who led assaults on power in the 19th century?",
                    "score": 0.689,
                    "answers": "www.alertadigital.com reported on 23/04/2019 that the Ministry of the Interior , friends of marching for lodges that led assaults on power in the 19th centurySpartero , Riego , O'Donnell , Prim , etc|ROOT\ton 23/04/2019|prep\t23/04/2019|pobj\tthat|mark\tthe|det\tthat the Ministry of the Interior , friends of marching for lodges that led assaults on power in the 19th centurySpartero , Riego , O'Donnell , Prim , etc|dobj\tof the Interior|prep\tthe|det\tthe Interior|pobj\t,|punct\tfriends of marching for lodges that led assaults on power in the 19th centurySpartero , Riego , O'Donnell , Prim , etc|appos\tof marching for lodges that led assaults on power in the 19th centurySpartero , Riego , O'Donnell , Prim , etc|prep\tmarching for lodges that led assaults on power in the 19th centurySpartero , Riego , O'Donnell , Prim , etc|pcomp\tfor lodges that led assaults on power in the 19th centurySpartero , Riego , O'Donnell , Prim , etc|prep\tlodges that led assaults on power in the 19th centurySpartero , Riego , O'Donnell , Prim , etc|pobj\tthat|nsubj\tthat led assaults on power in the 19th centurySpartero , Riego , O'Donnell , Prim , etc|relcl\ton power|prep\tpower|pobj\tin the 19th centurySpartero , Riego , O'Donnell , Prim , etc|prep\tthe|det\t19th|amod\tthe 19th centurySpartero , Riego , O'Donnell , Prim , etc|pobj\t,|punct\t,|punct\tO'Donnell , Prim , etc|conj\t,|punct\tPrim , etc|conj\t,|punct\tetc|conj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is Alertadigital.com?",
                    "score": 0.4997,
                    "answers": "www.alertadigital.com|nsubj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "All Masonsthe workers' redeemers, the proletarian messiahsThe left who cried out The left bourgeois whistling , saying that they cared about liberties, that they were democrats only if they won the elections, and The left even a civil war The left as the Bolshevik red flag was waved in Spain.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "What did the proletarian messiahs say about the left?",
                    "answer": "The left bourgeois whistling"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What did the Marxist left say about socialism?",
                    "score": 0.7167,
                    "answers": "All|det\t'|case\t,|punct\tproletarian|amod\tthe proletarian messiahsThe|appos\twho|nsubj\t,|punct\t,|punct\t,|punct\tand|cc\ta|det"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What did the left bourgeois say about socialism?",
                    "score": 0.7014,
                    "answers": "on 23/04/2019|prep"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Where was the Bolshevik red flag waving in Spain?",
                    "score": 0.6949,
                    "answers": "The left as the Bolshevik red flag was waved in Spain|appos"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What was the name of the left bourgeois who cried out they cared about liberties?",
                    "score": 0.5766,
                    "answers": "All Masonsthe workers '|poss"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "Nothing unusual under the red sun, as for murderers and torturers who raped nuns, dug up mummies, burned convents and churches, massacred in their Czech macabras, and executed for carrying a rosary and going to Mass without any remorse, organizing an electoral fraud was sinful minuta.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "What was organized by the murderers and torturers?",
                    "answer": "electoral fraud"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "Who organized the electoral fraud?",
                    "score": 0.7622,
                    "answers": "organizing an electoral fraud|csubj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "How were murderers and torturers massacred in their Czech macabras?",
                    "score": 0.7412,
                    "answers": "their Czech macabras|pobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What crimes were committed by murderers and torturers in Czech macabras?",
                    "score": 0.7155,
                    "answers": ",|punct\t,|punct\t,|punct\tchurches|conj\t,|punct\t,|punct\tgoing to Mass without any remorse|conj\tMass|pobj\t,|punct"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What was the purpose of carrying a rosary and going to mass without any remorse?",
                    "score": 0.611,
                    "answers": "carrying a rosary and going to Mass without any remorse|pcomp"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What was the punishment for the crimes committed by the murderers and torturers?",
                    "score": 0.6044,
                    "answers": "any remorse|pobj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "The pucherazo is but a light coup d'etat, decaf, since this is a deluxe pucherazo, fine cinnamon of supreme quality, the apotheosic climax so desired by the palace raiders, performance that is undoubtedly more spectacular to be left in the history books.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "What is the fine ingredient in the pucherazo?",
                    "answer": "cinnamon"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What type of coup d'etat is the pucherazo?",
                    "score": 0.8281,
                    "answers": "light|amod"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the performance of pucherazo?",
                    "score": 0.7453,
                    "answers": "a deluxe pucherazo , fine cinnamon of supreme quality , the apotheosic climax so desired by the palace raiders , performance that is undoubtedly more spectacular to be left in the history books|attr"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the name of the coup d'etat?",
                    "score": 0.7264,
                    "answers": "coup d'etat ,|nmod"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What are the history books about pucherazo?",
                    "score": 0.7181,
                    "answers": "the history books|pobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the pucherazo?",
                    "score": 0.7089,
                    "answers": "The pucherazo|nsubj\tdeluxe|amod"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "The left is also an expert in coup, because it is she who has starred in all, absolutely all, those that have taken place in contemporary Spain, since the National Uprising cannot be considered as such, because both the Republic and the Popular Front took power fraudulently, which deprives them of all legitimacy.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Who took power fraudulently?",
                    "answer": "the Republic and the Popular Front"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "How many coup took place in contemporary Spain?",
                    "score": 0.7338,
                    "answers": "on 23/04/2019|prep\t23/04/2019|pobj\tshe|attr\twho|nsubj\twho has starred in all , absolutely all , those that have taken place in contemporary Spain|ccomp\tin all , absolutely all , those that have taken place in contemporary Spain|prep\tall|det\tabsolutely|advmod\tall , absolutely all , those that have taken place in contemporary Spain|pobj\tthose that have taken place in contemporary Spain|appos\thave|aux\tthat have taken place in contemporary Spain|relcl\tcontemporary|amod\tcontemporary Spain|pobj\tsince|mark\tcan|aux\tboth|preconj\tall|det"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the history of the right and left in relation to coup?",
                    "score": 0.6923,
                    "answers": "The left|nsubj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Who is an expert in coup?",
                    "score": 0.6832,
                    "answers": "an expert in coup|attr"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What are the functions of the National Uprising?",
                    "score": 0.6724,
                    "answers": "power|dobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the National Uprising in contemporary Spain?",
                    "score": 0.6692,
                    "answers": "in contemporary Spain|prep"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "It is elementary that the left should be pucheril and coup, because its supposed moral superiority comes precisely from the fact that it can do all the misdeeds it wants with total impunity, because, lacking ethical principles and the slightest scruple, having no respect for the laws that do not favor its interests, by splashing in the Luciferina sewers of atrocious atheism, they can execute their frauds as whistling, as if it were the most natural thing in the world, feeling entitled to the coup and the pout, because they represent the people, they are progressive, and all that rubbish.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "How does the left feel about the coup and the pout?",
                    "answer": "they can execute their frauds as whistling, as if it were the most natural thing in the world,"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "Why should the left be pucheril and coup?",
                    "score": 0.7053,
                    "answers": "that It is elementary that the left should be pucheril and coup , because its supposed moral superiority comes precisely from the fact that it can do all the misdeeds it wants with total impunity , because , lacking ethical principles and the slightest scruple , having no respect for the laws that do not favor its interests , by splashing in the Luciferina sewers of atrocious atheism , they can execute their frauds as whistling , as if it were the most natural thing in the world , feeling entitled to the coup and the pout , because they represent the people , they are progressive , and all that rubbish|ccomp"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the purpose of the Luciferina sewers of atrocious atheism?",
                    "score": 0.678,
                    "answers": "the Luciferina sewers of atrocious atheism|pobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the definition of a coup and coup?",
                    "score": 0.6708,
                    "answers": "because they represent the people , they are progressive , and all that rubbish|advcl"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the source of evidence of the frauds committed by the left?",
                    "score": 0.6649,
                    "answers": "their frauds|dobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What are the laws that do not favor its interests?",
                    "score": 0.6647,
                    "answers": "the laws that do not favor its interests|pobj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "That is why the Left has never apologized for its barbassadas, for its innumerable crimes, and they give themselves the luxury of blaming their victims, as is the case with the iniquitous historical memory, for for for it the end justifies the means.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "What justifies the means?",
                    "answer": "the end"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What crimes did the Left commit?",
                    "score": 0.7064,
                    "answers": "for its barbassadas , for its innumerable crimes|prep\tfor its innumerable crimes|prep\tinnumerable|amod\tits innumerable crimes|pobj\tas is the case with the iniquitous historical memory|advcl"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What did the Left say about its barbassadas?",
                    "score": 0.6878,
                    "answers": "its barbassadas|pobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What does it mean to blame your victims for their innumerable crimes?",
                    "score": 0.6321,
                    "answers": "for for for it the end justifies the means|conj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the history of the Left?",
                    "score": 0.5413,
                    "answers": "the case with the iniquitous historical memory|nsubj\thistorical|amod"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the historical memory of the Left?",
                    "score": 0.5409,
                    "answers": "iniquitous|amod"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "In almost all the elections of the 20th century, all the victories of the left were due either to electoral fraud, or to a coup d'etat, explicit or not: The pact of San Sebastián of the year 1930, the coup d'etat of the elections of the year 31, when the monarchists handed power surprisingly to the Republicans when it was they who had won the elections, the coup d'etat of 1933 – when the left threatened an insurrection if it ruled the CEDA, which had obtained the majority in the elections –, the armed revolution of October of the year 34, the arousing fraud of the year 36..Since the Transition, all this democratic garbage of the pucherazos has continued, despite the fact that they are not sufficiently known, because modern electronic means allow to erase the traces of this misdemeanour, since it is no longer carried out the presentation of an electoral record showing brazen tachaduras, additions, scrapes and amendments, as happened in the fraudulent elections of the year 36.",
            "question_answers": [],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What were the results of the coup d'etat of 1933?",
                    "score": 0.6954,
                    "answers": "when it was they who had won the elections|advcl\twho had won the elections|ccomp\twhich had obtained the majority in the elections|relcl"
                },
                {
                    "question": "How many elections were there in the 20th century?",
                    "score": 0.6941,
                    "answers": "In almost all the elections of the 20th century|prep\talmost all the elections of the 20th century|pobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "How many votes did the CEDA win in the 1935 election?",
                    "score": 0.6898,
                    "answers": "the CEDA , which had obtained the majority in the elections|dobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What was the outcome of the 1935 election?",
                    "score": 0.6843,
                    "answers": "since it is no longer carried out the presentation of an electoral record showing brazen tachaduras , additions , scrapes and amendments , as happened in the fraudulent elections of the year 36|advcl"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What was the purpose of the coup d'etat?",
                    "score": 0.6819,
                    "answers": "a coup d'etat , explicit or not|pobj\tof the elections of the year 31|prep\tthe pucherazos|pobj\tthe fact that they are not sufficiently known|pobj\tthe traces of this misdemeanour|dobj\tof this misdemeanour|prep"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "Thus, the 23F was an authentic self-coup of state with which it was intended to favor the coming to power of the socialists, as well as the 11M, which allowed access to the power of the Zapatistas, and the same can be said of the coup hidden in the motion of fateful censorship that brought us the nauseating Sanchismo.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "What did www.alertadigital.com say about the 23F?",
                    "answer": "an authentic self-coup of state with which it was intended to favor the coming to power of the socialists,"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What was the purpose of the 23F coup?",
                    "score": 0.6804,
                    "answers": "www.alertadigital.com|nsubj\twww.alertadigital.com reported on 23/04/2019 that Thus , the 23F was an authentic self - coup of state with which it was intended to favor the coming to power of the socialists , as well as the 11 M , which allowed access to the power of the Zapatistas , and the same can be said of the coup hidden in the motion of fateful censorship that brought us the nauseating Sanchismo|ROOT\ton 23/04/2019|prep\t23/04/2019|pobj\tthat|mark\tThus|advmod\t,|punct\tthe|det\tthe 23F|nsubj\tthat Thus , the 23F was an authentic self - coup of state with which it was intended to favor the coming to power of the socialists , as well as the 11 M , which allowed access to the power of the Zapatistas , and the same can be said of the coup hidden in the motion of fateful censorship that brought us the nauseating Sanchismo|ccomp\tan|det\tauthentic|amod\tself|compound\t-|punct\tof state|prep\tstate|pobj\twith which|prep\twhich|pobj\tit|nsubjpass\twas|auxpass\twith which it was intended to favor the coming to power of the socialists , as well as the 11 M , which allowed access to the power of the Zapatistas|relcl\tto|aux\tto favor the coming to power of the socialists , as well as the 11 M , which allowed access to the power of the Zapatistas|xcomp\tthe|det\tthe coming to power of the socialists , as well as the 11 M , which allowed access to the power of the Zapatistas|dobj\tto power|prep\tpower|pobj\tof the socialists|prep\tthe|det\tthe socialists|pobj\t,|punct\tas|advmod\twell|advmod\tas well as|cc\tthe|det\tthe 11|conj\tM , which allowed access to the power of the Zapatistas|conj\t,|punct\twhich|nsubj\twhich allowed access to the power of the Zapatistas|relcl\taccess to the power of the Zapatistas|dobj\tto the power of the Zapatistas|prep\tthe|det\tthe power of the Zapatistas|pobj\tof the Zapatistas|prep\tthe|det\tthe Zapatistas|pobj\t,|punct\tand|cc\tthe|det\tthe same|nsubjpass\tcan|aux\tbe|auxpass\tthe same can be said of the coup hidden in the motion of fateful censorship that brought us the nauseating Sanchismo|conj\tthe|det\tthe coup hidden in the motion of fateful censorship that brought us the nauseating Sanchismo|pobj\thidden in the motion of fateful censorship|acl\tin the motion of fateful censorship|prep\tthe|det\tthe motion of fateful censorship|pobj\tof fateful censorship|prep\tfateful|amod\tfateful censorship|pobj\tthat|nsubj\tthat brought us the nauseating Sanchismo|relcl\tus|dative\tthe|det\tnauseating|amod\tthe nauseating Sanchismo|dobj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "Hit by blow, and not verse by verse, is how the Reds want to take our homeland to the Tartaros landfills, that is, the NOM.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "How did the Reds want to take their homeland to Tartaros landfills?",
                    "answer": "Hit by blow, and not verse by verse, is how the Reds want to take our homeland to the Tartaros landfills,"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What is the relationship between the Reds and Tartaros landfills?",
                    "score": 0.6441,
                    "answers": "www.alertadigital.com|nsubj\tblow|pobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What does the NOM stand for?",
                    "score": 0.6185,
                    "answers": "on 23/04/2019|prep\t23/04/2019|pobj\tthat|mark\tHit by blow , and not verse by verse ,|nsubj\t,|punct\tnot|neg\t,|punct\tthat Hit by blow , and not verse by verse , is the Reds want how to take our homeland to the Tartaros landfills , that is , the NOM|ccomp\thow|advmod\tthe Reds|nsubj\tthe Reds want how to take our homeland to the Tartaros landfills , that is , the NOM|ccomp\tto|aux\thow to take our homeland to the Tartaros landfills , that is , the NOM|xcomp\t,|punct\tthat|nsubj\tthat is|advmod\t,|punct"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the NOM?",
                    "score": 0.5753,
                    "answers": "www.alertadigital.com reported on 23/04/2019 that Hit by blow , and not verse by verse , is the Reds want how to take our homeland to the Tartaros landfills , that is , the NOM|ROOT\tthat is , the NOM|dobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the purpose of the NOM?",
                    "score": 0.5654,
                    "answers": "and|cc\tverse|pobj\tthe|det\tour|poss\tour homeland|dobj\tto the Tartaros landfills|prep\tthe|det\tthe Tartaros landfills|pobj\tthe|det"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "And along with the beatings, there are suspicions of punching: in 1993 there were serious irregularities in the census of some provinces, where whole right-wing neighborhoods were erased from the electoral census.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "What was erased from the electoral census in 1993?",
                    "answer": "whole right-wing neighborhoods"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "How many people were beat in the census in the province in 1993?",
                    "score": 0.6579,
                    "answers": "with the beatings|prep\tthe beatings|pobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What were the results of the census of some provinces in 1993?",
                    "score": 0.6488,
                    "answers": "along with the beatings|prep"
                },
                {
                    "question": "How many right wing neighborhoods were erased from the electoral census in 1993?",
                    "score": 0.6473,
                    "answers": "www.alertadigital.com reported on 23/04/2019 that And along with the beatings , there are suspicions of punching : in 1993 there were serious irregularities in the census of some provinces , where whole right - wing neighborhoods were erased from the electoral census|ROOT"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the source of evidence of the number of punching in the province of South Africa in 1993?",
                    "score": 0.6201,
                    "answers": "of punching|prep"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "In these elections the Electoral Board accused the PSOE of violating information neutrality, reaching limits that blushed to their own and strangers, according to the TVE workers themselves.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "On what date did alertadigital.com report that the PSOE was accused of violating information neutrality?",
                    "answer": "23/04/2019"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Who accused the PSOE of violating information neutrality?",
                    "answer": "the Electoral Board"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What did the Electoral Board accuse the PSOE of violating information neutrality?",
                    "score": 0.8398,
                    "answers": "www.alertadigital.com reported on 23/04/2019 that In these elections the Electoral Board accused the PSOE of violating information neutrality , reaching limits that blushed to their own and strangers , according to the TVE workers themselves|ROOT\ton 23/04/2019|prep\tthat In these elections the Electoral Board accused the PSOE of violating information neutrality , reaching limits that blushed to their own and strangers , according to the TVE workers themselves|ccomp\tthe PSOE|dobj\tof violating information neutrality , reaching limits that blushed to their own and strangers|prep\tviolating information neutrality , reaching limits that blushed to their own and strangers|pcomp"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What limits were reached by the Electoral Board?",
                    "score": 0.7206,
                    "answers": "limits that blushed to their own and strangers|dobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What limits did the PSOE reach to their own and strangers?",
                    "score": 0.7111,
                    "answers": "reaching limits that blushed to their own and strangers|advcl\tthat blushed to their own and strangers|relcl"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What did the TVE workers say about the claims?",
                    "score": 0.6902,
                    "answers": "according to the TVE workers themselves|prep"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What was the relationship between the PSOE and the TVE workers?",
                    "score": 0.6423,
                    "answers": "that|mark\tthe|det\tthe|det\t,|punct\tthat|nsubj\ttheir|poss\tand|cc\tstrangers|conj\t,|punct\tthe|det"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "The most typical thing about punching is that it affects those seats that are decided for a very small amount of votes.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "What is the most typical thing about punching?",
                    "answer": "that it affects those seats that are decided for a very small amount of votes"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "How many votes does punching affect?",
                    "score": 0.7847,
                    "answers": "www.alertadigital.com reported on 23/04/2019 that The most typical thing about punching is that it affects those seats that are decided for a very small amount of votes|ROOT\tthat The most typical thing about punching is that it affects those seats that are decided for a very small amount of votes|ccomp\tthat it affects those seats that are decided for a very small amount of votes|ccomp"
                },
                {
                    "question": "How many votes are needed to win a seat?",
                    "score": 0.7569,
                    "answers": "those seats that are decided for a very small amount of votes|dobj\tthat are decided for a very small amount of votes|relcl"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the most common thing about punching?",
                    "score": 0.7031,
                    "answers": "The most typical thing about punching|nsubj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is Alertadigital.com?",
                    "score": 0.5924,
                    "answers": "www.alertadigital.com|nsubj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "In this sense, the most suspicious elections were those of 1996, where polls skated in a loud way, winning Jose María Aznar only for fifteen seats, when the polls gave him a far greater advantage.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "When did alertdigital.com report that the most suspicious elections were in 1996?",
                    "answer": "23/04/2019"
                },
                {
                    "question": "How many seats did Aznar win in 1996?",
                    "answer": "fifteen"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What did polls say about Jose María Aznar's election in 1996?",
                    "score": 0.7976,
                    "answers": "most suspicious|amod"
                },
                {
                    "question": "How many seats did Jose María Aznar win in the 1996 election?",
                    "score": 0.7735,
                    "answers": "on 23/04/2019|prep\t23/04/2019|pobj\tIn this sense|prep\tthis sense|pobj\tthe most suspicious elections|nsubj\tin a loud way|prep\ta loud way|pobj\tMaría|compound\tonly for fifteen seats|prep\tfifteen seats|pobj\twhen the polls gave him a far greater advantage|advcl\ta far greater advantage|dobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is Alertadigital.com?",
                    "score": 0.5284,
                    "answers": "www.alertadigital.com|nsubj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "This last-minute vote change was very significant, as well as suspicious, as there was a spectacular turnaround at the last moment of the vote.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "What was the last minute vote change?",
                    "answer": "last-minute"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "How many votes were there during the last moment of the election in 2019?",
                    "score": 0.7457,
                    "answers": "that|mark\tThis|det"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What was the outcome of the last minute vote change?",
                    "score": 0.7008,
                    "answers": "last - minute|compound"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "The height of the hills is that these red messiahs also cheat among themselves, organizing pucherazos even in the same primaries that organize to elect their leaders.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "What type of elections do the red messiahs organize to elect their leaders?",
                    "answer": "primaries"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "Who organized pucherazos even in the same primaries that organized to elect leaders?",
                    "score": 0.8511,
                    "answers": "these|det\tthemselves|pobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What did the red messiahs cheat on themselves with?",
                    "score": 0.7752,
                    "answers": "among themselves|prep"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What are the red messiahs doing to elect their leaders?",
                    "score": 0.7724,
                    "answers": "www.alertadigital.com reported on 23/04/2019 that The height of the hills is that these red messiahs also cheat among themselves , organizing pucherazos even in the same primaries that organize to elect their leaders|ROOT\tthat organize to elect their leaders|relcl"
                },
                {
                    "question": "How many pucherazos were organized in the same primaries?",
                    "score": 0.727,
                    "answers": "organizing pucherazos even in the same primaries that organize to elect their leaders|advcl"
                },
                {
                    "question": "How many pucherazos are there in the primaries?",
                    "score": 0.7198,
                    "answers": "even in the same primaries that organize to elect their leaders|prep"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "It is well known the scandal that Zapatero organized when he was elected as the PSOE leader in Leon, arriving to put ballot boxes in the cemeteries so that the dead could vote for him.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Who was elected as the PSOE leader in Leon?",
                    "answer": "Zapatero"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "How many ballots did Zapatero put in the cemeteries?",
                    "score": 0.7326,
                    "answers": "ballot boxes|dobj\tin the cemeteries|prep"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Did Zapatero put ballot boxes in the cemeteries so that the dead could vote for him?",
                    "score": 0.7193,
                    "answers": "so|mark"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What did Zapatero do to help the dead vote?",
                    "score": 0.7179,
                    "answers": "the cemeteries|pobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What was the name of the scandal that Zapatero organized when he was elected as the PSOE leader?",
                    "score": 0.7164,
                    "answers": "on 23/04/2019|prep\t23/04/2019|pobj\tthat|mark\tIt|nsubjpass\twell|advmod\tthe|det\tthat|dobj\twhen|advmod\the|nsubjpass\twas|auxpass\tthe|det\t,|punct\tthe|det\tthat|mark\tthe|det"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What was the purpose of putting ballotboxes in cemeteries?",
                    "score": 0.668,
                    "answers": "to put ballot boxes in the cemeteries so that the dead could vote for him|advcl"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "But we hadn't seen anything yetexcept for the ultramegagolpist Largo Caballerobecause pucheril perfection is in Sanchez, a liar and dancer, perfectus detritus de la dictacracia, Rasputin quasi tavernario, a Faustic character like Luis candelas, felon, megalomaniac, narcissist..as much as adjectives I put it, I will never stop describing him as he deserves, but undoubtedly the one that best fits him is the one dedicated to him by many articulists: psychopath.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "When did alertdigital.com report that we hadn't seen anything except for the ultramegagolpist Largo Caballero?",
                    "answer": "23/04/2019"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Which ultramegagolpist did we see on 23/04/2019?",
                    "answer": "Largo Caballero"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "Who is Largo Caballerobecause pucheril perfection is in Sanchez?",
                    "score": 0.7713,
                    "answers": "www.alertadigital.com|nsubj\ton 23/04/2019|prep\t23/04/2019|pobj\tn't|neg\tthe ultramegagolpist|compound\tLargo|compound\tpucheril|amod\ta liar and dancer|appos\tdancer|conj\tperfectus|nmod\tdetritus|nmod\tperfectus detritus de la dictacracia|appos\tRasputin|nmod\tquasi|amod\tRasputin quasi tavernario|appos\ta Faustic character like Luis candelas , felon , megalomaniac , narcissist|appos\tLuis|compound\tLuis candelas , felon , megalomaniac , narcissist|pobj\tas much as adjectives I put it|advmod\tas adjectives I put it|prep\tadjectives I put it|pobj\tI put it|relcl\tas he deserves|advcl\tthe one that best fits him|nsubj\tthat best fits him|relcl\tundoubtedly the one that best fits him is the one dedicated to him by many articulists : psychopath|conj\tthe one dedicated to him by many articulists|attr\tdedicated to him by many articulists|acl\tto him|prep\tby many articulists|agent\tmany articulists|pobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the best description of Largo Caballerobecause pucheril perfection?",
                    "score": 0.7637,
                    "answers": "as much as adjectives I put it , I will never stop describing him as he deserves , but undoubtedly the one that best fits him is the one dedicated to him by many articulists : psychopath|ROOT"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the relationship between Luis candelas and megalomaniac?",
                    "score": 0.7461,
                    "answers": "like Luis candelas , felon , megalomaniac , narcissist|prep"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Who is Largo Caballerobecause?",
                    "score": 0.7447,
                    "answers": "yetexcept for the ultramegagolpist Largo Caballerobecause|advmod\tfor the ultramegagolpist Largo Caballerobecause|prep\tthe ultramegagolpist Largo Caballerobecause|pobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is Largo Caballerobecause about pucheril perfection?",
                    "score": 0.7431,
                    "answers": "that But we had n't seen anything pucheril perfection is in Sanchez , a liar and dancer , perfectus detritus de la dictacracia , Rasputin quasi tavernario , a Faustic character like Luis candelas , felon , megalomaniac , narcissist yetexcept for the ultramegagolpist Largo Caballerobecause|ccomp"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "From caste comes to the greyhound, as Sánchez starred in an alevoso pucherazo at the same headquarters of Ferraz in October 2016, when, behind a screen, and without any authorization, Sánchez's supporters began a vote in an urn on the holding of an extraordinary express Congress.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "What did Sánchez's supporters vote in?",
                    "answer": "an urn on the holding of an extraordinary express Congress"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "Where did Sánchez starred in an alevoso pucherazo?",
                    "score": 0.7105,
                    "answers": "at the same headquarters of Ferraz|prep\tthe same headquarters of Ferraz|pobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Where did Sánchez star in alevoso pucherazo?",
                    "score": 0.693,
                    "answers": "www.alertadigital.com reported on 23/04/2019 that From caste comes to the greyhound , as Sánchez starred in an alevoso pucherazo at the same headquarters of Ferraz in October 2016 , when , behind a screen , and without any authorization , Sánchez 's supporters began a vote in an urn on the holding of an extraordinary express Congress|ROOT"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What did Sánchez's supporters say about the holding of an extraordinary express Congress?",
                    "score": 0.6467,
                    "answers": "October 2016 , when , behind a screen , and without any authorization , Sánchez 's supporters began a vote in an urn on the holding of an extraordinary express Congress|pobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What did Sánchez do in alevoso pucherazo?",
                    "score": 0.6045,
                    "answers": "in an alevoso pucherazo|prep"
                },
                {
                    "question": "How many supporters of Sánchez were there in October 2016?",
                    "score": 0.5565,
                    "answers": "Sánchez 's supporters|nsubj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "Vote without control, without censors, without intervention, this pucheraz provoked disgust and tears even among the members closest to it.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "What did the pucheraz cause among the members closest to it?",
                    "answer": "disgust"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "How did the pucheraz cause disgust and tears among members closest to it?",
                    "score": 0.739,
                    "answers": "disgust and tears|dobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What did the Pucheraz do without censors?",
                    "score": 0.6821,
                    "answers": "without control , without censors , without intervention|prep"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What was the vote without control without censors?",
                    "score": 0.6688,
                    "answers": "that Vote without control , without censors , without intervention , this pucheraz provoked disgust and tears even among the members closest to it|ccomp"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the relationship between voting without control and censors?",
                    "score": 0.6117,
                    "answers": "that|mark\tcontrol|pobj\t,|punct\twithout censors|prep\t,|punct\twithout intervention|prep\tintervention|pobj\t,|punct\tthis|det\tand|cc\teven|advmod\tthe|det\tclosest to it|amod\tto it|prep\tit|pobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the source of evidence of the Pucheraz vote without control?",
                    "score": 0.5949,
                    "answers": "tears|conj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "Then came his doctoral thesis, pucherazo cum laude, but it is not necessary to forget his activity in Caja Madrid at the same time of the scandal of the preferential ones, neither the plugs to the Begoñísima, nor that it was surrounded by a cabinet cum fraud without parallel, where many of its components are addicted to the fiscal pucheras of creating ghost societies to evade taxes.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "What are the fiscal pucheras doing to evade taxes?",
                    "answer": "creating ghost societies"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "Who did Pucherazo cum laude work for?",
                    "score": 0.7913,
                    "answers": "the Begoñísima|pobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What was Pucherazo cum laude?",
                    "score": 0.7659,
                    "answers": "on 23/04/2019|prep\t23/04/2019|pobj\tthat|mark\tThen|advmod\this|poss\t,|punct\tcum laude|appos\t,|punct\tbut|cc\tit|nsubj\tit is not necessary to forget his activity in Caja Madrid at the same time of the scandal of the preferential ones , neither the plugs to the Begoñísima , nor that it was surrounded by a cabinet cum fraud without parallel , where many of its components are addicted to the fiscal pucheras of creating ghost societies to evade taxes|conj\tnot|neg\tnecessary|acomp\tto|aux\tto forget his activity in Caja Madrid at the same time of the scandal of the preferential ones , neither the plugs to the Begoñísima , nor that it was surrounded by a cabinet cum fraud without parallel , where many of its components are addicted to the fiscal pucheras of creating ghost societies to evade taxes|xcomp\this|poss\this activity in Caja Madrid at the same time of the scandal of the preferential ones , neither the plugs to the Begoñísima , nor that it was surrounded by a cabinet cum fraud without parallel , where many of its components are addicted to the fiscal pucheras of creating ghost societies to evade taxes|dobj\tin Caja Madrid|prep\tat the same time of the scandal of the preferential ones , neither the plugs to the Begoñísima , nor that it was surrounded by a cabinet cum fraud without parallel , where many of its components are addicted to the fiscal pucheras of creating ghost societies to evade taxes|prep\tthe|det\tsame|amod\tthe same time of the scandal of the preferential ones , neither the plugs to the Begoñísima , nor that it was surrounded by a cabinet cum fraud without parallel , where many of its components are addicted to the fiscal pucheras of creating ghost societies to evade taxes|pobj\tthe|det\tthe scandal of the preferential ones , neither the plugs to the Begoñísima , nor that it was surrounded by a cabinet cum fraud without parallel , where many of its components are addicted to the fiscal pucheras of creating ghost societies to evade taxes|pobj\tthe|det\t,|punct\tneither|preconj\tthe|det\tneither the plugs to the Begoñísima , nor that it was surrounded by a cabinet cum fraud without parallel , where many of its components are addicted to the fiscal pucheras of creating ghost societies to evade taxes|dep\tthe|det\t,|punct\tnor|cc\tthat|mark\tit|nsubjpass\twas|auxpass\tthat it was surrounded by a cabinet cum fraud without parallel , where many of its components are addicted to the fiscal pucheras of creating ghost societies to evade taxes|conj\tby a cabinet cum fraud without parallel , where many of its components are addicted to the fiscal pucheras of creating ghost societies to evade taxes|agent\ta|det\t,|punct\twhere|advmod\tof its components|prep\tits|poss\tare|auxpass\tthe|det\tghost|compound\tto|aux"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What was the purpose of pucherazo cum laude?",
                    "score": 0.706,
                    "answers": "many of its components|nsubjpass"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is pucherazo cum laude?",
                    "score": 0.6875,
                    "answers": "www.alertadigital.com reported on 23/04/2019 that Then came his doctoral thesis , pucherazo cum laude , but it is not necessary to forget his activity in Caja Madrid at the same time of the scandal of the preferential ones , neither the plugs to the Begoñísima , nor that it was surrounded by a cabinet cum fraud without parallel , where many of its components are addicted to the fiscal pucheras of creating ghost societies to evade taxes|ROOT\tthat Then came his doctoral thesis , pucherazo cum laude , but it is not necessary to forget his activity in Caja Madrid at the same time of the scandal of the preferential ones , neither the plugs to the Begoñísima , nor that it was surrounded by a cabinet cum fraud without parallel , where many of its components are addicted to the fiscal pucheras of creating ghost societies to evade taxes|ccomp\tdoctoral|amod\this doctoral thesis , pucherazo cum laude|nsubj\tpucherazo|appos\tcum|nmod\tof the scandal of the preferential ones , neither the plugs to the Begoñísima , nor that it was surrounded by a cabinet cum fraud without parallel , where many of its components are addicted to the fiscal pucheras of creating ghost societies to evade taxes|prep\tpreferential|amod\ta cabinet cum fraud without parallel , where many of its components are addicted to the fiscal pucheras of creating ghost societies to evade taxes|pobj\tcum|nmod\twhere many of its components are addicted to the fiscal pucheras of creating ghost societies to evade taxes|relcl\tto the fiscal pucheras of creating ghost societies to evade taxes|prep\tthe fiscal pucheras of creating ghost societies to evade taxes|pobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the source of evidence of Pucherazo cum laude?",
                    "score": 0.6803,
                    "answers": "www.alertadigital.com|nsubj\tits components|pobj\ttaxes|dobj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "The PSOE raised this evil crow that seeks to take our eyes, our moneys, and the Spains.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Who raised the evil crow that seeks to take our eyes, our moneys, and the Spains?",
                    "answer": "The PSOE"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What did the PSOE say about the crow?",
                    "score": 0.7861,
                    "answers": "The|det\tthat The PSOE raised this evil crow that seeks to take our eyes , our moneys , and the Spains|ccomp\tto|aux\tand|cc"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the name of the crow that the PSOE raised?",
                    "score": 0.7091,
                    "answers": "www.alertadigital.com reported on 23/04/2019 that The PSOE raised this evil crow that seeks to take our eyes , our moneys , and the Spains|ROOT\tthat|mark\tthis|det\tthat|nsubj\t,|punct\t,|punct\tthe|det"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What are the Spains?",
                    "score": 0.6838,
                    "answers": "the Spains|conj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the purpose of a crow?",
                    "score": 0.6674,
                    "answers": "that seeks to take our eyes , our moneys , and the Spains|relcl"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the relationship between the PSOE and the crow?",
                    "score": 0.6639,
                    "answers": "The PSOE|nsubj\tour|poss\tour|poss"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "In his impressive career as a macarra rasputinesca, the icing was the coup d'etat he disguised with the motion of censure.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "On what date did alertadigital.com report that the coup d'etat was disguised with the motion of censure?",
                    "answer": "23/04/2019"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What was the coup d'etat he disguised with the motion of censure?",
                    "answer": "the icing"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What was the purpose of the coup d'etat?",
                    "score": 0.7317,
                    "answers": "that In his impressive career as a macarra rasputinesca , the icing was the coup d'etat he disguised with the motion of censure|ccomp\tcoup|nmod\tthe coup d'etat he disguised with the motion of censure|attr\the disguised with the motion of censure|relcl\twith the motion of censure|prep\tthe motion of censure|pobj\tof censure|prep"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What was the name of the coup d'etat that Macarra rasputinesca participated in?",
                    "score": 0.6973,
                    "answers": "that|mark\tmacarra|compound\tthe|det\tthe|det\tthe|det\tcensure|pobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is Alertadigital.com?",
                    "score": 0.519,
                    "answers": "www.alertadigital.com|nsubj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "Such a sinister character, with a total lack of scruples, is more than willing to falsify an election, to organize the punch that it takes for no one to get him out of his Falcon, would be missing more.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Who reported on 23/04/2019 that Such a sinister character is more than willing to falsify an election?",
                    "answer": "www.alertadigital.com"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "How many scruples are there in a conspiracy to falsify an election?",
                    "score": 0.7604,
                    "answers": "Such a sinister character , with a total lack of scruples ,|nsubj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "How long did it take to get out of a falcon?",
                    "score": 0.73,
                    "answers": "the punch that it takes for no one to get him out of his Falcon|dobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "How many scrupters are there in an election?",
                    "score": 0.6753,
                    "answers": "would be missing more|ccomp"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What are scruples?",
                    "score": 0.5978,
                    "answers": "scruples|pobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the method used to get him out of his cage?",
                    "score": 0.5902,
                    "answers": "more than willing to falsify an election , to organize the punch that it takes for no one to get him out of his Falcon , would be missing more|acomp"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "Can anyone doubt it?Now, in a country like Spain, is it possible that a pucheraz can be produced?The reality is that, since Tezanos arrived at the CIS, every month we are attending a pucheraso of law, with those crazy polls that yield scandalously rigged results in favor of the PSOE, which they do not believe themselves.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "What is it possible to produce in a country like Spain?",
                    "answer": "pucheraz"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What are the results of the pucheraso of law in favor of the PSOE?",
                    "answer": "scandalously rigged results"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What polls have been conducted in favor of the PSOE?",
                    "score": 0.8853,
                    "answers": "of the PSOE , they do not believe which themselves|prep"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What polls have shown that Tezanos rigged results in favor of PSOE?",
                    "score": 0.8832,
                    "answers": "reality is that , since Tezanos arrived at the CIS , every month we are attending a pucheraso of law , with those crazy polls that yield scandalously rigged results in favor of the PSOE , they do not believe which themselves|ROOT"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Is it possible that a pucheraz can be produced?",
                    "score": 0.8698,
                    "answers": "possible|acomp\tthat a pucheraz can be produced?The|ccomp"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What type of pucheraz can be produced in a country like Spain?",
                    "score": 0.8119,
                    "answers": "a pucheraz|nsubjpass"
                },
                {
                    "question": "When did Tezanos arrive at the CIS?",
                    "score": 0.8108,
                    "answers": "since Tezanos arrived at the CIS|advcl"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "But, spinning thinner, one wonders whether these predictions are but a way to make a possible socialist punch more credible, advancing those incredible results so that later, when they materialize, they do not cause so much as amazement or indignation, using the tactics of the already said, and arguing that the hidden vote was of the PSOE.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Who reported on 23/04/2019 that the predictions are a way to make a possible socialist punch more credible?",
                    "answer": "www.alertadigital.com"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What could the predictions be used to make more credible?",
                    "answer": "socialist punch"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What tactics did the socialists use to achieve their socialist punch?",
                    "score": 0.7448,
                    "answers": "the tactics of the already said|dobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What tactics were used to make the socialist punch more credible?",
                    "score": 0.707,
                    "answers": "already|advmod"
                },
                {
                    "question": "How credible is the socialist punch?",
                    "score": 0.671,
                    "answers": "a possible socialist punch more credible|ccomp"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What was the secret vote of the PSOE in 2019?",
                    "score": 0.6267,
                    "answers": "www.alertadigital.com reported on 23/04/2019 that But , spinning thinner , one wonders whether these predictions are but a way to make a possible socialist punch more credible , advancing those incredible results so that later , when they materialize , they do not cause so much as amazement or indignation , using the tactics of the already said , and arguing that the hidden vote was of the PSOE|ROOT\targuing that the hidden vote was of the PSOE|conj\thidden|amod\tthat the hidden vote was of the PSOE|ccomp\tof the PSOE|prep\tthe PSOE|pobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the source of evidence of the votes of the socialists in 2019?",
                    "score": 0.6172,
                    "answers": "these predictions|nsubj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "Naturally, in the elections of 28-A there will be acts of picaresca, not to mention otherwise, on the part of supporters of the left against ballots of center-right: theft, manipulations in order to turn them into invalid ballots, harassment at the exit of the governors of the schools after the writing of the minutes.. A whole host of macarrero acts in which the left is so expert.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "What is an example of an act of picaresca?",
                    "answer": "harassment at the exit of the governors of the schools"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the name of the act in which the left is so expert?",
                    "answer": "macarrero"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "How many crimes were committed in the elections of 28-A?",
                    "score": 0.6855,
                    "answers": "A whole host of macarrero acts in which the left is so expert|ROOT"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What are the acts of picaresca?",
                    "score": 0.6713,
                    "answers": "www.alertadigital.com|nsubj\twww.alertadigital.com reported on 23/04/2019 that Naturally , in the elections of 28 - A there will be acts of picaresca , not to mention otherwise , on the part of supporters of the left against ballots of center - right : theft , manipulations in order to turn them into invalid ballots , harassment at the exit of the governors of the schools after the writing of the minutes ..|ROOT\ton 23/04/2019|prep\t23/04/2019|pobj\tthat|mark\tNaturally|advmod\t,|punct\tin the elections of 28 - A|prep\tthe|det\tthe elections of 28 - A|pobj\tof 28 - A|prep\t28|nummod\t-|punct\t28 - A|pobj\tthere|expl\twill|aux\tthat Naturally , in the elections of 28 - A there will be acts of picaresca , not to mention otherwise , on the part of supporters of the left against ballots of center - right : theft , manipulations in order to turn them into invalid ballots , harassment at the exit of the governors of the schools after the writing of the minutes|ccomp\tacts of picaresca , not to mention otherwise , on the part of supporters of the left against ballots of center - right : theft , manipulations in order to turn them into invalid ballots , harassment at the exit of the governors of the schools after the writing of the minutes|attr\tof picaresca|prep\tpicaresca|pobj\t,|punct\tnot|neg\tto|aux\tnot to mention otherwise|cc\totherwise|advmod\t,|punct\tthe|det\tthe part of supporters of the left|pobj\tof supporters of the left|prep\tsupporters of the left|pobj\tof the left|prep\tthe|det\tthe left|pobj\tagainst ballots of center - right|prep\tballots of center - right|pobj\tof center - right|prep\tcenter|compound\t-|punct\tcenter - right|pobj\t:|punct\ttheft , manipulations in order to turn them into invalid ballots , harassment at the exit of the governors of the schools after the writing of the minutes|appos\t,|punct\tmanipulations in order to turn them into invalid ballots|appos\tin order to turn them into invalid ballots|prep\torder to turn them into invalid ballots|pobj\tto|aux\tto turn them into invalid ballots|acl\tthem|dobj\tinto invalid ballots|prep\tinvalid|amod\tinvalid ballots|pobj\t,|punct\tat the exit of the governors of the schools|prep\tthe|det\tthe exit of the governors of the schools|pobj\tof the governors of the schools|prep\tthe|det\tthe governors of the schools|pobj\tof the schools|prep\tthe|det\tthe schools|pobj\tafter the writing of the minutes|prep\tthe|det\tthe writing of the minutes|pobj\tof the minutes|prep\tthe|det\t..|punct\tA|det\twhole|amod\tin which|prep\twhich|pobj\tthe|det\tthe left|nsubj\tin which the left is so expert|relcl\tso|advmod\tso expert|acomp"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What are the political acts of picaresca?",
                    "score": 0.6706,
                    "answers": "of macarrero acts in which the left is so expert|prep"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What are the crimes of the left against ballots of center-right?",
                    "score": 0.6559,
                    "answers": "macarrero acts in which the left is so expert|pobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "How many people were expelled from the schools after the writing of the minutes?",
                    "score": 0.6202,
                    "answers": "harassment at the exit of the governors of the schools after the writing of the minutes|appos"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "There may even be zombies who abandon their tannatories and fields to exercise their democratic right.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Why do zombies abandon their tannatories and fields?",
                    "answer": "to exercise their democratic right"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What is the definition of a zombie?",
                    "score": 0.6607,
                    "answers": "zombies who abandon their tannatories and fields to exercise their democratic right|attr\ttheir tannatories and fields|dobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the democratic right of a zombie?",
                    "score": 0.6571,
                    "answers": "who abandon their tannatories and fields to exercise their democratic right|relcl"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the source of evidence of how many zombies abandon their tannatories and fields to exercise their democratic right?",
                    "score": 0.6545,
                    "answers": "that|mark\tThere|expl\tmay|aux\teven|advmod\ttheir|poss\tand|cc\tto|aux\ttheir|poss"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is Alertadigital.com?",
                    "score": 0.5201,
                    "answers": "www.alertadigital.com|nsubj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "Nor should it be ruled out that all immigrants who can, even if they do not have the right to vote, should be included in the census, since it is clear that this group is voting on the left.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Who reported on 23/04/2019 that Nor should it be ruled out that all immigrants should be included in the census?",
                    "answer": "www.alertadigital.com"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What should be included in the census?",
                    "answer": "all immigrants who can, even if they do not have the right to vote, should be included in the census,"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "Why should immigrants be included in the census?",
                    "score": 0.8555,
                    "answers": "Nor|cc\tthat all immigrants who can , even if they do not have the right to vote , should be included in the census , since it is clear that this group is voting on the left|ccomp\tin the census|prep"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What are the voting rights of immigrants who can not vote?",
                    "score": 0.7802,
                    "answers": "who can , even if they do not have the right to vote ,|relcl"
                },
                {
                    "question": "How many immigrants are voting on the left?",
                    "score": 0.7592,
                    "answers": "that this group is voting on the left|ccomp"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the voting age of non-immigrants?",
                    "score": 0.7193,
                    "answers": "who|nsubj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What does Alertadigital.com say about voting rights?",
                    "score": 0.7089,
                    "answers": "that|mark\tshould|aux\tthat|mark\tif|mark\tthe right to vote|dobj\tto|aux\tto vote|acl\tshould|aux\tthat|mark\tthis|det\tthis group|nsubj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "For putting up a case, we already had the Guadalajara scandal.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "In what city was a scandal reported on on 23/04/2019 by www.alertadigital.com?",
                    "answer": "Guadalajara"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What was the Guadalajara scandal?",
                    "score": 0.8166,
                    "answers": "www.alertadigital.com|nsubj\ton 23/04/2019|prep\t23/04/2019|pobj\tthat|mark\tFor putting up a case|prep\tputting up a case|pcomp\tup|prt\ta|det\ta case|dobj\t,|punct\twe|nsubj\tthat For putting up a case , we already had the Guadalajara scandal|ccomp\tthe|det\tthe Guadalajara scandal|dobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the Guadalajara scandal?",
                    "score": 0.7764,
                    "answers": "www.alertadigital.com reported on 23/04/2019 that For putting up a case , we already had the Guadalajara scandal|ROOT\talready|advmod"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "But while it is highly unlikely that the votes of polling stations can be manipulated, since everything is done by hand, the same is not the case when the results of the electoral records are sent to the Matrix of the Ministry of the Interior, where the company in charge of counting the votes and awarding the seats will be located, since this process is carried out by a company, which is well aware of the cracks and fissures through which the votes can be changed, a process which, moreover, will be in the hands of a handful of people.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Who reported on 23/04/2019 that it is highly unlikely that the votes of polling stations can be manipulated?",
                    "answer": "www.alertadigital.com"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is a company well aware of?",
                    "answer": "cracks and fissures"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "How many votes can be manipulated?",
                    "score": 0.6695,
                    "answers": "highly unlikely|acomp\tthat the votes of polling stations can be manipulated|ccomp"
                },
                {
                    "question": "How many people are able to manipulate the votes?",
                    "score": 0.6602,
                    "answers": "which , moreover , will be in the hands of a handful of people|relcl\tthe hands of a handful of people|pobj\tof a handful of people|prep\ta handful of people|pobj\tof people|prep"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the process used to count votes?",
                    "score": 0.6582,
                    "answers": "while|mark\twhile it is highly unlikely that the votes of polling stations can be manipulated , since everything is done by hand|advcl\tpolling|compound\tpolling stations|pobj\tcan|aux\tand|cc\tby a company , which is well aware of the cracks and fissures through which the votes can be changed , a process which , moreover , will be in the hands of a handful of people|agent\tand|cc\tcan|aux\tthrough which the votes can be changed|relcl"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Who is in charge of counting votes and awarding seats?",
                    "score": 0.6389,
                    "answers": "of the Interior|prep"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is Alertadigital.com?",
                    "score": 0.5106,
                    "answers": "www.alertadigital.com|nsubj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "Surprisingly, for the elections, the State has terminated the contract with Indra, the traditional company that has been in charge of this task for quite some time, and that, despite the fact that it has not been able to avoid suspicions in some electoral processes in which it intervenedin Hispanic America above allit was doing badly that its task was well.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "What race did Indra intervene in?",
                    "answer": "Hispanic America"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "Did the state terminate the contract with Indra?",
                    "score": 0.8035,
                    "answers": "not|neg"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the relationship between the state of Florida and the company that was in charge of the elections?",
                    "score": 0.6481,
                    "answers": "that , despite the fact that it has not been able to avoid suspicions in some electoral processes in which it intervenedin Hispanic America above allit was doing badly|conj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "Now the dealership is the company SCYTL, also Catalan and linked to George Soros, which organized an electronic vote election in Switzerland that turned out to be a fiasco, for its lack of security.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Where was the election held?",
                    "answer": "Switzerland"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "Who organized the electronic vote election in Switzerland?",
                    "score": 0.7555,
                    "answers": "to George Soros , which organized an electronic vote election in Switzerland that turned out to be a fiasco , for its lack of security|prep\twhich organized an electronic vote election in Switzerland that turned out to be a fiasco , for its lack of security|relcl\tin Switzerland|prep"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is SCYTL's relationship with George Soros?",
                    "score": 0.5665,
                    "answers": "its lack of security|pobj\tof security|prep\tsecurity|pobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the relationship between SCYTL and George Soros?",
                    "score": 0.5281,
                    "answers": "that Now the dealership is the company SCYTL , also Catalan and linked to George Soros , which organized an electronic vote election in Switzerland that turned out to be a fiasco , for its lack of security|ccomp\tout|prt"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is SCYTL?",
                    "score": 0.4937,
                    "answers": "www.alertadigital.com|nsubj\twww.alertadigital.com reported on 23/04/2019 that Now the dealership is the company SCYTL , also Catalan and linked to George Soros , which organized an electronic vote election in Switzerland that turned out to be a fiasco , for its lack of security|ROOT\ton 23/04/2019|prep\t23/04/2019|pobj\tthat|mark\tNow|advmod\tthe|det\tthe dealership|nsubj\tthe|det\tthe company SCYTL , also Catalan and linked to George Soros , which organized an electronic vote election in Switzerland that turned out to be a fiasco , for its lack of security|attr\tSCYTL ,|appos\t,|punct\talso|advmod\talso Catalan and linked to George Soros , which organized an electronic vote election in Switzerland that turned out to be a fiasco , for its lack of security|amod\tand|cc\tlinked to George Soros , which organized an electronic vote election in Switzerland that turned out to be a fiasco , for its lack of security|conj\tGeorge|compound\tGeorge Soros , which organized an electronic vote election in Switzerland that turned out to be a fiasco , for its lack of security|pobj\t,|punct\twhich|nsubj\tan|det\telectronic|amod\tvote|compound\tan electronic vote election in Switzerland that turned out to be a fiasco , for its lack of security|dobj\tthat|nsubj\tthat turned out to be a fiasco , for its lack of security|relcl\tto|aux\tto be a fiasco , for its lack of security|xcomp\ta|det\ta fiasco|attr\t,|punct\tfor its lack of security|prep\tits|poss"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "But the pearl of this possible hacking that awaits us is in the anti-hacking decree that has been pulled out of the sleeve of the government, in order to protect the electoral results from possible cyber attacks, claiming that they have already occurred in some elections in other countries.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "On what date was the anti-hacking decree issued?",
                    "answer": "23/04/2019"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Where is the pearl of this possible hacking that awaits us?",
                    "answer": "in the anti-hacking decree that has been pulled out of the sleeve"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What did the anti-hacking decree say about election results?",
                    "score": 0.7272,
                    "answers": "that has been pulled out of the sleeve of the government , in order to protect the electoral results from possible cyber attacks , claiming that they have already occurred in some elections in other countries|relcl\tclaiming that they have already occurred in some elections in other countries|advcl"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What was the anti-hacking decree?",
                    "score": 0.6705,
                    "answers": "23/04/2019|pobj\tout of the sleeve of the government|prep\tpossible cyber attacks|pobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What does the anti-hacking decree entail?",
                    "score": 0.6669,
                    "answers": "that But the pearl of this possible hacking that awaits us is in the anti - hacking decree that has been pulled out of the sleeve of the government , in order to protect the electoral results from possible cyber attacks , claiming that they have already occurred in some elections in other countries|ccomp"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What was the purpose of the anti-hacking decree?",
                    "score": 0.6402,
                    "answers": "that|mark\tBut|cc\tthe|det\tthe pearl of this possible hacking that awaits us|nsubj\tthis|det\tpossible|amod\tthat|nsubj\tthe|det\t-|amod\tthat|nsubjpass\thas|aux\tbeen|auxpass\tthe|det\tthe|det\t,|punct\tto|aux\tto protect the electoral results from possible cyber attacks ,|acl\tthe|det\telectoral|amod\tthe electoral results|dobj\tpossible|amod\tcyber|compound\t,|punct\tthat|mark\tthey|nsubj\thave|aux\talready|advmod\tsome|det\tother|amod"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the anti-hacking decree?",
                    "score": 0.6388,
                    "answers": "in the anti - hacking decree that has been pulled out of the sleeve of the government , in order to protect the electoral results from possible cyber attacks , claiming that they have already occurred in some elections in other countries|prep"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "According to this decree, a new body - the Sub-Committee on Information Security in Electoral Processes, attached to the Higher Committee for Information Security - consisting of six senior officials appointed by the Government, will draw up a protocol against the falsification of electoral data, and will have the power to suspend the publication of provisional data on the ballot, which means that we may not know the results until a couple of days later, when the final data are given, passing a margin of two days in the interim during which the results can be cooked.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Who reported on 23/04/2019 that a new body - the Sub-Committee on Information Security in Electoral Processes, attached to the Higher Committee for Information Security - would draw up a protocol against the falsification of electoral data?",
                    "answer": "www.alertadigital.com"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the name of the new body that will draw up a protocol against the falsification of electoral data?",
                    "answer": "the Sub-Committee on Information Security in Electoral Processes, attached to the Higher Committee for Information Security"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What did the new body do to suspend the publication of provisional data on the ballot?",
                    "score": 0.7902,
                    "answers": "that According to this decree , a new body - the Sub - Committee on Information Security in Electoral Processes , attached to the Higher Committee for Information Security - consisting of six senior officials appointed by the Government , will draw up a protocol against the falsification of electoral data , and will have the power to suspend the publication of provisional data on the ballot , which means that we may not know the results until a couple of days later , when the final data are given , passing a margin of two days in the interim during which the results can be cooked|ccomp"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the process for falsification of electoral data?",
                    "score": 0.7558,
                    "answers": "electoral|amod"
                },
                {
                    "question": "How long did it take to know the results of the election?",
                    "score": 0.7283,
                    "answers": "consisting of six senior officials appointed by the Government|acl\tof six senior officials appointed by the Government|prep\twill have the power to suspend the publication of provisional data on the ballot , which means that we may not know the results until a couple of days later , when the final data are given , passing a margin of two days in the interim during which the results can be cooked|conj\tthe power to suspend the publication of provisional data on the ballot , which means that we may not know the results until a couple of days later , when the final data are given , passing a margin of two days in the interim during which the results can be cooked|dobj\twhich means that we may not know the results until a couple of days later , when the final data are given , passing a margin of two days in the interim during which the results can be cooked|advcl\tthat we may not know the results until a couple of days later , when the final data are given , passing a margin of two days in the interim during which the results can be cooked|ccomp\tuntil a couple of days later , when the final data are given|prep\ta couple of days|npadvmod\tof days|prep\tdays|pobj\tof two days in the interim during which the results can be cooked|prep\ttwo days in the interim during which the results can be cooked|pobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What was the purpose of creating the Sub-committee on Information Security in Electoral Processes?",
                    "score": 0.7266,
                    "answers": "to this decree|prep\tby the Government|agent"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the method used to suspend the release of provisional data?",
                    "score": 0.7245,
                    "answers": "the ballot|pobj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "Another suspicion lies in the obvious fact that it will not be possible to know with certainty the veracity of that alleged attack by the hackers, or its extent, if it actually occurs.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "What is another suspicion of the hackers?",
                    "answer": "it will not be possible to know with certainty the veracity of that alleged attack"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What did hackers say about the attack by hackers?",
                    "score": 0.8483,
                    "answers": "of that alleged attack by the hackers|prep"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the veracity of the alleged attack by hackers?",
                    "score": 0.7507,
                    "answers": "www.alertadigital.com reported on 23/04/2019 that Another suspicion lies in the obvious fact that it will not be possible to know with certainty the veracity of that alleged attack by the hackers , or its extent , if it actually occurs|ROOT\tthat|mark\tAnother|det\tthat Another suspicion lies in the obvious fact that it will not be possible to know with certainty the veracity of that alleged attack by the hackers , or its extent , if it actually occurs|ccomp\tin the obvious fact that it will not be possible to know with certainty the veracity of that alleged attack by the hackers , or its extent , if it actually occurs|prep\tthe|det\tobvious|amod\tthe obvious fact that it will not be possible to know with certainty the veracity of that alleged attack by the hackers , or its extent , if it actually occurs|pobj\tthat|mark\tit|nsubj\twill|aux\tnot|neg\tthat it will not be possible to know with certainty the veracity of that alleged attack by the hackers , or its extent , if it actually occurs|acl\tpossible|acomp\tto|aux\tto know with certainty the veracity of that alleged attack by the hackers , or its extent , if it actually occurs|xcomp\twith certainty|prep\tcertainty|pobj\tthe|det\tthe veracity of that alleged attack by the hackers , or its extent ,|dobj\tthat|det\talleged|amod\tby the hackers|prep\tthe|det\tthe hackers|pobj\t,|punct\tor|cc\tits|poss\t,|punct\tif|mark\tit|nsubj\tactually|advmod\tif it actually occurs|advcl"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the relationship between hackers and hackers?",
                    "score": 0.7105,
                    "answers": "Another suspicion|nsubj\tits extent ,|conj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the source of evidence of the hackers that attacked Alertadigital?",
                    "score": 0.6378,
                    "answers": "23/04/2019|pobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is Alertadigital.com?",
                    "score": 0.5506,
                    "answers": "www.alertadigital.com|nsubj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "Under what criteria will it be determined whether or not to suspend provisional scrutiny?What guarantees of reliability does a computer program have that clearly admits its weakness to a cyber attack on the Ministry of the Interior, or its website?The case is that we will have two days of darkness where Spain will be in the belly of the whale, from a monstrous Matrix, from which another Popular Front can emerge.",
            "question_answers": [],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What guarantees does a computer program have that admit its weakness to a cyberattack on the Ministry of the Interior or its website?",
                    "score": 0.8077,
                    "answers": "reliability|pobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What does Alertadigital.com say about a computer program?",
                    "score": 0.7204,
                    "answers": "www.alertadigital.com|nsubj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What are the guarantees of reliability of a computer program?",
                    "score": 0.6991,
                    "answers": "a computer program|nsubj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "How many days of darkness will Spain be in the belly of the whale?",
                    "score": 0.6408,
                    "answers": "case is that we will have two days of darkness where Spain will be in the belly of the whale , from a monstrous Matrix , from which another Popular Front can emerge|ROOT\tthat we will have two days of darkness where Spain will be in the belly of the whale , from a monstrous Matrix , from which another Popular Front can emerge|ccomp\ttwo|nummod\ttwo days of darkness where Spain will be in the belly of the whale , from a monstrous Matrix , from which another Popular Front can emerge|dobj\twhere Spain will be in the belly of the whale , from a monstrous Matrix , from which another Popular Front can emerge|relcl"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What are the criteria for whether or not to suspend provisional scrutiny?",
                    "score": 0.6402,
                    "answers": "Under what criteria|prep\twhat criteria|pcomp"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "Just as no one in his right mind would buy Sanchez a used car, it is impossible for a citizen aware minimally of his rufianesque calaña not to harbour suspicion that this psychopath is willing to everything in order to continue to feel the unceasing caress of the Monclovita velvet.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "What velvet did alertdigital.com report Sanchez was willing to everything in order to continue to feel the caress of?",
                    "answer": "Monclovita"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What is the condition of a used car?",
                    "score": 0.6249,
                    "answers": "a used car|dobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the relationship between Sanchez and the caress of the Monclovita velvet?",
                    "score": 0.5808,
                    "answers": "that|mark\tJust|advmod\tas|mark\tno|det\tin his right mind|prep\this|poss\tright|amod\this right mind|pobj\twould|aux\ta|det\tused|amod\t,|punct\tit|nsubj\timpossible|acomp\tfor|mark\ta|det\this|poss\tnot|neg\tto|aux\tthat|mark\tthis|det\tthis psychopath|nsubj\tto|aux\tto everything|xcomp\tin|mark\torder|dep\tto|aux\tto|aux\tthe|det\tthe|det"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the Monclovita velvet?",
                    "score": 0.5491,
                    "answers": "the Monclovita velvet|pobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the rufianesque calaña?",
                    "score": 0.5112,
                    "answers": "his rufianesque calaña|pobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the name of the rufianesque calaña?",
                    "score": 0.5087,
                    "answers": "aware minimally of his rufianesque calaña|amod\tof his rufianesque calaña|prep"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "The possibility that Sánchez is plotting something fat is a rumor that grows with the passing of the days, even from people close to the Moncloa, an unstoppable runrun that sets many patriots on the edge, a tidal wave that threatens to turn into reality the nightmare of attending a red-separate revolution in Spain, which would undoubtedly lead us to a pre-war situation.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "What is the Moncloa rumored to be?",
                    "answer": "a tidal wave that threatens to turn into reality the nightmare of attending a red-separate revolution"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What would happen if Sánchez attended a red-separate revolution in Spain?",
                    "score": 0.6664,
                    "answers": "to turn into reality the nightmare of attending a red - separate revolution in Spain , which would undoubtedly lead us to a pre - war situation|xcomp"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the source of evidence of Sánchez planning to attend a red separate revolution in Spain?",
                    "score": 0.6498,
                    "answers": "the Moncloa , an unstoppable runrun that sets many patriots on the edge , a tidal wave that threatens to turn into reality the nightmare of attending a red - separate revolution in Spain , which would undoubtedly lead us to a pre - war situation|pobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is Sánchez planning to do with the Moncloa river?",
                    "score": 0.6461,
                    "answers": "a rumor that grows with the passing of the days , even from people close to the Moncloa , an unstoppable runrun that sets many patriots on the edge , a tidal wave that threatens to turn into reality the nightmare of attending a red - separate revolution in Spain , which would undoubtedly lead us to a pre - war situation|attr\teven from people close to the Moncloa , an unstoppable runrun that sets many patriots on the edge , a tidal wave that threatens to turn into reality the nightmare of attending a red - separate revolution in Spain , which would undoubtedly lead us to a pre - war situation|prep"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the relationship between Sánchez and the Red-separate revolution in Spain?",
                    "score": 0.5721,
                    "answers": "to a pre - war situation|prep"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "And it is that the PSOE, that of the hundred years of beating and barbarism, that of the thousand and a pucherazos, can be defined perfectly with this sentence of the movie Death among the flowers: It is a cheater, just like his brother.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Who reported on 23/04/2019 that the PSOE is a cheater?",
                    "answer": "www.alertadigital.com"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the name of the movie that defines the PSOE?",
                    "answer": "Death among the flowers"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "How many pucherazos were in the movie Death among the flowers?",
                    "score": 0.5653,
                    "answers": "of the thousand and a pucherazos|prep\tthe thousand and a pucherazos|pobj\ta pucherazos|conj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is a cheater?",
                    "score": 0.5475,
                    "answers": "a cheater , just like his brother|attr"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the relationship between the PSOE and barbarism?",
                    "score": 0.5471,
                    "answers": "the PSOE , that of the hundred years of beating and barbarism , that of the thousand and a pucherazos ,|nsubjpass\tbarbarism|conj"
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}